"use strict";(self.webpackChunkiec_61499_curriculum=self.webpackChunkiec_61499_curriculum||[]).push([[991],{5666:(e,s,t)=>{t.r(s),t.d(s,{assets:()=>u,contentTitle:()=>c,default:()=>d,frontMatter:()=>i,metadata:()=>l,toc:()=>C});var r=t(4848),n=t(8453),a=t(445);const o=JSON.parse('[{"questionText":"What does ERP stand for?","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"Efficient Resource Planning","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Enterprise Resource Planning","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"Engineering Resource Protocol","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Enterprise Resource Planning (answer)","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"Which system acts as the central hub for data across business functions?","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"MES","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"ERP System","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"PLC","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"SCADA","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"What is the full form of MES in a manufacturing context?","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"Management Execution Service","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Manufacturing Execution System","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"Mechanical Engineering System","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Material Evaluation System","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"Which system schedules tasks on a production line?","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"CRM","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"MES","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"ERP","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"DCS","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"What role do PLCs play in car manufacturing?","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"Personnel Logistics Control","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Controlling assembly line machinery","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"Product Lifecycle Management","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Packaging and Labeling Control","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"Which system monitors the assembly line\'s real-time status?","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"MES","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"SCADA System","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"ERP","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"CRM","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"What does SCADA stand for?","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"Systematic Control and Data Acquisition","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Standard Control and Data Analysis","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Supervisory Control and Data Acquisition","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"Secure Control and Data Allocation","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"What does a DCS manage in a manufacturing environment?","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"Data Collection Services","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Direct Communication Systems","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Control of Complex or hazardous processes","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"All the above","isCorrect":true}]},{"questionText":"Which system handles delivery logistics after manufacturing?","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"SCADA","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"MES","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"ERP System","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"CRM","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"Which industrial communication could connect PLCs and SCADA?","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"HTTP, SMTP, FTP","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Modbus, PROFIBUS","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"TCP/IP, UDP","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"HTML, CSS","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"What is the main function of field devices?","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"To provide Wi-Fi connectivity","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"To interact with the physical process","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"To facilitate employee communication","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"To secure the manufacturing area","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"Which system processes customizations and creates a Bill of Materials (BOM)?","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"DCS","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"ERP System","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"MES","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"SCADA","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"What does \'genealogy\' signify in MES?","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"Family history of the employees","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"History and location of parts","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"Genetic research in manufacturing","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Generational change in technology","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"Who notifies the customer that their car is being delivered?","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"MES","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"DCS","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"The delivery service","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"CRM component of the ERP System","isCorrect":true}]},{"questionText":"What does BI stand for, and which system provides it?","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"Business Integration","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Business Intelligence","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"Business Information","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Business Improvement","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"How does MES manage quality?","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"By extensive manual inspection","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Outsourcing to third-party quality control","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Through quality management features","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"By customer feedback post-production","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"Which system coordinates device control with PLCs?","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"CRM","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"MES","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"ERP","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"SCADA","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"What does MES track in labor management?","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"The number of employees","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Salary distributions","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"Labor skills and certifications","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"Work-break schedules","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"What ERP system tools analyze production efficiency after delivery?","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"ERP management tools","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"BI tools","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"ERP planning tools","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"ERP operational tools","isCorrect":false}]}]'),i={sidebar_position:2},c="TBD",l={id:"Module2/quiz",title:"TBD",description:"",source:"@site/docs/Module2/quiz.md",sourceDirName:"Module2",slug:"/Module2/quiz",permalink:"/IEC61499-Curriculum/docs/Module2/quiz",draft:!1,unlisted:!1,editUrl:"https://github.com/AIC3Lab/IEC61499-Curriculum/docs/Module2/quiz.md",tags:[],version:"current",sidebarPosition:2,frontMatter:{sidebar_position:2},sidebar:"tutorialSidebar",previous:{title:"Ecosystem of Industrial Automation Systems",permalink:"/IEC61499-Curriculum/docs/Module2/pptx"},next:{title:"TBD",permalink:"/IEC61499-Curriculum/docs/Module2/video"}},u={},C=[];function x(e){const s={h1:"h1",...(0,n.R)(),...e.components};return(0,r.jsxs)(r.Fragment,{children:[(0,r.jsx)(s.h1,{id:"tbd",children:"TBD"}),"\n","\n",(0,r.jsx)(a.A,{questions:o})]})}function d(e={}){const{wrapper:s}={...(0,n.R)(),...e.components};return s?(0,r.jsx)(s,{...e,children:(0,r.jsx)(x,{...e})}):x(e)}},445:(e,s,t)=>{t.d(s,{A:()=>a});var r=t(6540),n=t(4848);function a(e){let{questions:s}=e;const[t,a]=(0,r.useState)(Array(s.length).fill(null)),[o,i]=(0,r.useState)(!1),[c,l]=(0,r.useState)(0);return(0,n.jsxs)("div",{className:"quiz",children:[s.map(((e,r)=>(0,n.jsxs)("div",{className:"question-section",children:[(0,n.jsxs)("div",{className:"question-count",children:[(0,n.jsxs)("span",{children:["Question ",r+1]}),"/",s.length]}),(0,n.jsx)("div",{className:"question-text",children:e.questionText}),(0,n.jsx)("div",{className:"answer-section",children:e.answerOptions.map(((e,o)=>(0,n.jsx)("button",{onClick:()=>((e,r,n)=>{const o=[...t];o[e]={isCorrect:r,selectedAnswerIndex:n,correctAnswerIndex:s[e].answerOptions.findIndex((e=>e.isCorrect))},a(o),r&&l(c+1)})(r,e.isCorrect,o),disabled:null!==t[r],className:t[r]?o===t[r].selectedAnswerIndex?t[r].isCorrect?"correct":"incorrect":o===t[r].correctAnswerIndex?"correct":"":"",children:e.answerText},o)))})]},r))),!o&&(0,n.jsx)("button",{onClick:()=>{i(!0)},children:"Show Results"}),o&&(0,n.jsxs)("div",{className:"score-section",children:["You scored ",c," out of ",s.length]})]})}},8453:(e,s,t)=>{t.d(s,{R:()=>o,x:()=>i});var r=t(6540);const n={},a=r.createContext(n);function o(e){const s=r.useContext(a);return r.useMemo((function(){return"function"==typeof e?e(s):{...s,...e}}),[s,e])}function i(e){let s;return s=e.disableParentContext?"function"==typeof e.components?e.components(n):e.components||n:o(e.components),r.createElement(a.Provider,{value:s},e.children)}}}]);